Burak Yıldırım

Software Developer

✓ yldrmburak1167@gmail.com

+905416592910

in burak-yildrm

BurakYildrm

Final-year university student specializing in web development, with 2 years of JavaScript experience and a 6-month role as a Full-Stack Developer. My time in the Erasmus+ program broadened my cultural understanding and communication skills. With a solid academic foundation and hands-on experience, I'm dedicated to delivering topnotch web solutions. I'm looking for a role where I can use my skills to benefit both myself and a forward-thinking company.

Professional Experience

07/2023 – 08/2023 Istanbul, Turkey

Frontent Developer Intern

OBSS

- Gained insights into best practices for frontend development, ensuring maintainable and efficient code.
- Developed a contact form management application utilizing Next.js, MongoDB and Tailwind CSS.

01/2023 – 06/2023 Istanbul, Turkey

Full-Stack Developer

Andasis

- Contributed to both the frontend and backend development of the modem devices.
- Used JavaScript, Python, and Git.
- Gained experience working with Agile methodology.

08/2022 – 12/2022 Istanbul, Turkey

Embedded Software Engineer

Andasis

- Contributed to the network protocols used in modem devices.
- Used C and OpenWRT.

Education

09/2019 – present

Gebze Technical University

Kocaeli, Turkey Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering

02/2022 - 05/2022 Le Kremlin-Bicêtre, **EPITA**

Erasmus+ Exchange Program

France

Skills

- JavaScript & TypeScript & Next.js & Vue.js
- Python & Java
- Git

- HTML & CSS & Tailwind CSS
- MongoDB & PostgreSQL & Firebase
- Agile

Languages

English (C1) | **French** (A1) | **Turkish** (Native)

Certificates

• freeCodeCamp - JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures 🛮

Projects

FormFlow (Next.js)

A web application that is used to manage the user feedback

Carpetiem (Vue.js)

A web application that is used to keep track of the carpets after they've been handed to the carpet cleaners

Hex Game (Java) 🛮

A hex game developed for Android